Guide to the Juanita Morris Kreps Papers, 1921-2001 and undated RL.00789
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Speeches Series, 1962-1999 and undated, 18 boxes
  - Incomes of the Aged: The Case for a Broader Perspective, U.S. Senate Committee on Aging, 1968 Mar. (Box 33)
  - On Reaching the Stars by Midnight, Visiting Scholars of Assoc. of Eastern North Carolina College, 1968 (Box 33)
  - Women Who Work: Why and Where? Women and Work, 1968 Nov. (Box 33)
  - The Position of the Older Worker in the American Labor Force, Cornell University, 1969 July 30 (Box 33)
  - Double Jeopardy: Old Age and Low Incomes, Duke Campus Club, 1969 Apr. (Box 33)
  - American Psychological Association, 1969 Sept. 2 (Box 33)
  - Meeting for Parents with Staff, Duke University, 1969 Sept. 16 (Box 33)
  - The Quiet Poor: Old Age in America, Conference of National Organizations, 1969 Oct. (Box 33)
  - American Economic Association, 1969 Dec. 28 (Box 33)
  - The Secretary of the Seventies, National Secretaries Association, 1970 Jan. 19 (Box 33)
  - The Relevance of Today's Education: An Economist's View, address to Angier B. Dukes, 1970 Feb. (Box 33)
  - What Shall We Do after We're Liberated? Valkyries of UNC-CH, 1970 Mar. (Box 33)
  - Remarks to the Alumni at Columbia, S.C., 1970 Mar. 26 (Box 33)
  - What It's Like to Have a Sophomore Daughter, Duke Woman's College, 1970 Apr. 11 (Box 33)
  - Work and Leisure Options, Industrial Gerontology Seminar, Annapolis, MD, 1970 Apr. 26-30 (Box 33)
  - Higher Education in the 1970s, Alumni Weekend, 1970 Jun. 6 (Box 33)
  - Youth Unemployment and Minimum Wage, North American Conference on labor statistics, Houston, Texas, 1970 Jun. 11 (Box 33)
  - What are Women on Campus Up To? American Association of University Women (AAUW), Meredith College, 1970 Jun. (Box 33)
  - On the Problem of Being Young, University of Colorado, 1970 July 9 (Box 33)
  - On the Time Allocation of Work and Income, Gerontology Institute, Bethesda, MD, 1970 Aug. 25 (Box 33)
  - Notes on Crisis and Conflict, Alumnae Association of Duke Woman's College, 1970 Nov. 5 (Box 33)
  - Working Wives: A View of the 1970s, Divinity, Law and Medical School Dames, 1971 Feb. 16 (Box 33)
  - The Changing Concept of Work, Sweet Briar College honors convocation, 1971 Feb. 17 (Box 33)
  - On the Economics of Aging, Institute - New York State College of Human Ecology, 1971 Mar. 23 (Box 33)
  - Can You Afford to Grow Old? Seattle, Washington, 1971 Mar. 31-Apr. 1 (Box 33)
  - Sex in the Marketplace: American Women at Work, National Secretaries' Association, Washington, D.C., 1971 Apr. 21 (Box 33)
  - Nontraditional Students: The Case of Mrs. Smith, Commission on Academic Affairs, American Council on Education, 1971 May 16-17 (Box 33)
  - On Financing Retirement, American Psychological Association, Washington, D.C., 1971 Sept. 4 (Box 33)
  - The Value of Women's Work, Greensboro YWCA, 1971 Oct. 7 (Box 33)
  - Work and Income Over the Life Cycle, Society of Actuaries - Toronto, Canada, 1971 Nov. 10 (Box 34)
  - Economic Equality for Women: Requisites and Realities, American Economic Association meeting, New Orleans, La., 1971 Dec. (Box 34)
  - A Comment of Joe Katz's Challenge to "Body of Knowledge" Learning from Person-Centered Advocates, Association of American College, Washington, D.C., 1972 Jan. 9-11 (Box 34)
  - Work and Income Through the Lifespan, Chapel Hill Financial Series, 1972 Jan. 20 (Box 34)
  - Unemployment and Underemployment of Women Workers, Joint Economic Committee Hearings, U.S. Congress, 1972 Feb. 23 (Box 34)
  - Chicago Alumni, 1972 Jan. 24 (Box 34)
  - On the Problem of Being Young, University of Arizona, Graduate Committee on Gerontology, 1972 Apr. 14 (Box 34)
  - American Psychiatric Association, Dallas, Texas, 1972 May 1 (Box 34)
  - National Council Alumni Weekend, 1972 May 20 (Box 34)
  - On Running the World, commencement address - Pomona College, Claremont, California, 1972 June 4 (Box 34)
  - Femininity Has Nothing to Do With It, Randolph-Macon, 1972 Sept. 4 (Box 34)
  - Women in Business: Femininity has Nothing to do with It, Bryant College - Symposium for the Advancement of Women in Business, 1972 Oct. 11 (Box 34)
  - Sex in the Marketplace, University of Michigan speech, 1972 Oct. 18 (Box 34)
  - Gerontological Society Meeting, San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1972 Dec. 17-21 (Box 34)
  - The Right of Women to Work, Duke Univ., Conference for Teachers of Social Studies, 1973 Mar. 3 (Box 34)
  - The Economics of Wifehood, University of Florida, 1973 Mar. 8 (Box 34)
  - Unemployment and Underemployment of Women Workers, UNC-Greensboro, 1973 Apr. 12 (Box 34)
  - Money and Leisure after Fifty, Case Western Reserve University, 1973 Apr. 19 (Box 34)
  - Between Work and Old Age, Leisure or Limbo? Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1973 Apr. 25-27 (Box 34)
  - YWCA - Chicago, 1973 May 9 (Box 34)
  - The Price of Ignorance, UNC commencement speech, 1973 May 13 (Box 34)
  - A World I Never Made, commencement - Cornell College, Mount Vernon, Iowa, 1973 May 20 (Box 34)
  - The Price of Ignorance, Denison University, 1973 May 23 (Box 34)
  - Conference on Successful Aging, 1973 June 9 (Box 34)
  - The Occupations: Wider Economic Opportunity for Women, The University of Georgia, Athens, 1973 Aug. 2 (Box 34)
  - University of S. Cal. at L.A., Notes on the Economics of Aging, 1973 Oct. 9 (Box 34)
  - Denison, Friedman-Samuelson Panel, 1973 Oct. 26 (Box 34)
  - Sex in the Marketplace, Banks Research Conference, 1973 Nov. 23 (Box 34)
  - The Economics of Old Age, Trial Magazine Article, 1974 Jan. 4 (Box 34)
  - Higher Education in a Steady State: Some Productivity and Manpower Questions, Princeton, 1974 (Box 34)
  - Sex in the Marketplace and Early Retirement: Pressures and Resistance, University of Tennessee, 1974 Jan. 15 (Box 34)
  - The Economics of Old Age, Sandhill Regional Library, 1974 Feb. 19 (Box 34)
  - Unemployment and Underemployment of Women Workers, Washington and Lee, 1974 Feb. 21 (Box 34)
  - The Aged in an Age of Ambivalence, Tucson, Ariz., Western Gerontological Society, "The Aged in an Age of Ambivalence," 1974 Mar. 24 (Box 34)
  - Future Careers for College Women, Hollins College, 1974 Apr. 3 (Box 34)
  - Sex in the Marketplace, Garth Mangum, 1974 Apr. 9-10 (Box 34)
  - The Time Paradigm, UNC-G commencement address, 1974 May 12 (Box 35)
  - Work, Leisure, and Education: Toward Greater Flexibility through the Lifespan, Madrid, 1974 June (Box 35)
  - Youth and the Meaning of Work, Freshman Lecture, 1974 Sept. 2 (Box 35)
  - The Aged in an Age of Ambivalence, Bowdoin College, 1974 Oct. (Box 35)
  - Social Policy and Individual Achievement, Markle Foundation, 1974 Sept. 29-Oct. 1 (Box 35)
  - Help! There's a Woman in the Boardroom, Junior League of Durham, 1974 Nov. (Box 35)
  - Help! There's a Woman in the Boardroom, Friends of Claremont College, 1974 Nov. 6 (Box 35)
  - Who is Responsible for the Quality of Life? NYU, 1975 Mar. 13 (Box 35)
  - Who is Responsible for the Quality of Life? NYU Lecture 1975 Mar. 13 (Box 35)
  - The Economy and the Learning Environment, Nat'l Association of Student Personnel Administrators, 1975 Mar. 31 (Box 35)
  - Does it Pay to Go to College? Symposium on the Work of the Carnegie Commission, 1975 Apr. (Box 35)
  - Women in Academia: Today is Different, Olin Conference, Washington University, 1975 Apr. 16-17 (Box 35)
  - A Time for Learning to Think, Durham Academy commencement, 1975 June 6 (Box 35)
  - 10th International Congress of Gerontology, Jerusalem, 1975 June 22-27 (Box 35)
  - On Knowledge, Love, and Ignorance, St. Lawrence University, 1975 Sept. (Box 35)
  - Early Retirement: Pressures and Resistance, Randolph-Macon, 1975 Oct. 9-10 (Box 35)
  - Old Age: A Period of Dignity or Dependency, Louisville-Courier, 1975 Oct. 22 (Box 35)
  - Human Values, Economic Values, and the Elderly, Case Western Reserve, 1975 Nov. 10-13 (Box 35)
  - Social Security in the Coming Decade: Questions for a Minute System, Robert Ball Lecture, 1975 Nov. 18 (Box 35)
  - The Economic Status of Women in the United Statesin International Women's Year, American Economic Association, 1975 Dec. 29 (Box 35)
  - Some Time Dimensions of Manpower Policy, N.C.M.P., 1976 Jan. (Box 35)
  - Help! There is a Woman in the Boardroom, Rotary - Winston-Salem, 1975 Feb. 3 (Box 35)
  - Income in Retirement: Problems for the Economy and the Individual, Leonard Davis School of Gerontology, 1976 Feb. 17 (Box 35)
  - 1976: A World Turned Upside Down, North Carolina Citizen's Association (Benjamin Franklin Portrait to NC Museum of Art), 1976 Mar. 24, 2 folders (Box 35)
  - Learning and Earning: Some New Questions, ODK, 1976 Apr. 3 (Box 35)
  - What Shall We Do Now that We are Liberated? and Mother Goose, Wheaton Edition, Wheaton College, 1976 May 29-30 (Box 35)
  - A Look to the 1980s, Duke University, Alumni Seminar, 1976 Sept. 25 (Box 35)
  - Age, Work, and Income, S.E.A. presidential address, Atlanta, 1976 Nov. 19 (Box 35)
  - After 200 Years: A Perspective on Disenchantment, American Council of Life Insurance, 1976 Nov. (Box 35)
  - Social Programs and the Costs of Higher Education: Who Should Pay? Western Electric proposal, 1976 (Box 36)
  - Learning and Earning: Some New Questions, AAHE meeting, 1976 (Box 36)
  - A Note on Freedom and Constraints, Duke University commencement, 1977 May 8 (Box 36)
  - After One Hundred Days: Reflections of a Harried Secretary, Women's Forum, Duke University, 1977 May 14 (Box 36)
  - Thoughts about Government and Business, Vital Speeches, 1977 Aug. 1 (Box 36)
  - Ode to an Educated Man, University of Oklahoma, 1978 May 13 (Box 36)
  - Shaping Economic Policy for the Decade, Raleigh Executive Club, 1980 Jan. 14 (Box 36)
  - Speech made to the Duke administrators, 1980 Feb. 6 (Box 36)
  - Untitled, Duke University Medical School speech, 1980 Mar. (Box 36)
  - Duke Business School Groundbreaking, 1980 Mar. 21 (Box 36)
  - Economics: A Discipline in Disarray? Mead Lecture, Trinity College, 1980 Apr. 16 (Box 36)
  - Welfare speech, Middlebury, Vt., 1980 Apr. 18 (Box 36)
  - Berea speech, 1980 Apr. 25 (Box 36)
  - 1979: Last Year's Surprises, Vanderbilt speech, 1980 May 1 (Box 36)
  - U.S. Trade Policy: Issues for the Eighties, Hungary speech, 1980 May 7-9 (Box 36)
  - Hungarian speech material, 1980 May 8, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - Tulane University, 1980 May 9 (Box 36)
  - 1980 and Beyond: What Lies Ahead for American Business, Mead Corporation, 1980 May 15, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - Rochester Human Relations speech, 1980 May 21 (Box 36)
  - Colgate University Hamilton, N.Y., acceptance of honorary degree, 1980 May 25 (Box 36)
  - Charlotte Latin School, 1980 May 26 (Box 37)
  - Consumer Affairs Forum, J.C. Penney, New York, 1980 June 4 (Box 37)
  - 1980 and Beyond: What Lies Ahead for American Business, Fifty's Group, RTP, 1980 June 16 (Box 37)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt: Yesterday's Advice, Today's Problems, Eleanor Roosevelt Award, 1980 Aug. 6 (Box 37)
  - State of the Economy: 1980, National Passenger Traffic Association, New Orleans, La., 1980 Sept. 14 (Box 37)
  - Shaping Economic Policy for the Decade, Duke major speakers, Duke University, 1980 Sept. 15 (Box 37)
  - Winston-Salem Kiwanis Club, 1980 Sept. 18 (Box 37)
  - World Trade in the '80s: Can America Compete? financial executives, San Francisco, Calif., 1980 Oct. 8 (Box 37)
  - State of the Economy: 1980, Blue Cross/Blue Shield, Hot Springs, Virginia, 1980 Oct. 17 (Box 37)
  - Business Regulation in a Changing Economy, Ray Bloch Production, Houston, 1980 Oct. 29 (Box 37)
  - Luncheon, Berea N.Y. Alumni, 1980 Nov. 6 (Box 37)
  - Shaping Economic Policy for the Decade, UNC-Greensboro, Bryan Lecture, 1980 Nov. 11 (Box 37)
  - Shaping Economic Policy for the Decade, Foundation for Student Communication, Princeton University, New York, 1980 Nov. 25 (Box 37)
  - Shaping Economic Policy for the Decade, executive seminar, Kingsport, Tenn., 1980 Dec. 9 (Box 37)
  - Choosing Work that Matters, Rochester Institute of Technology, 1980 Dec. 11 (Box 37)
  - 1980-81 Council on Aging and Human Development series, 1980 Jan. 13 (Box 37)
  - U.S. Trade Problems in the 80's, RJR, Sandpiper Bay, Fla., 1981 Jan. 18-19, 2 folders (Box 37)
  - The Perils of Policy-making: A Retrospective Look, Women's Forum, N. Y., Marymount Manhattan College, 1981 Feb. 6 (Box 38)
  - What I Hope You are Studying, Emory University, women MBA students, 1981 Feb. 11 (Box 38)
  - Greensboro Section, National Council of Jewish Women, 1981 Mar. 2 (Box 38)
  - The Perils of Policy-making: A Retrospective Look, University of Utah and Brigham Young University, 1981 Mar. 5-7 (Box 38)
  - Women's Economic Round Table, Waldorf-Astoria, 1981 Mar. 18 (Box 38)
  - The Perils of Policy Making: A Retrospective Look, Indiana State University, Terre Haute, Ind., 1981 Apr. 1-2 (Box 38)
  - Institute of Policy Studies, Duke, 1981 Apr. 3 (Box 38)
  - Farewell to Superwoman, Pan-Hellenic Council Regional Conference, 1980 Apr. 4 (Box 38)
  - Furman and Duke Endowment, Marsh and Mclennan Lecture, 1981 Apr. 7-8 (Box 38)
  - Exciting Work, Not Certain Answers, Bentley College commencement, Waltham, Mass., 1981 May 16 (Box 38)
  - Farewell to Superwoman, Winston-Salem YWCA, 1981 May 21 (Box 38)
  - A Time for Leadership, Trinity College commencement, Hartford, Conn., 1981 May 24 (Box 38)
  - A Small World: National and International Views of the Future, Governor's kick off program, archives and history auditorium, 1981 June 1 (Box 38)
  - State of the Economy, Education Dept. School Management Conference, 1981 June 21 (Box 38)
  - AAUW Achievement Award, 1981 June 22 (Box 38)
  - Armco women luncheon, 1981 June 25 (Box 39)
  - Toward Corporate Leadership for Women, Smith College management program graduation, 1981 Aug. 7 (Box 39)
  - The Perils of Policymaking, Casper Lecture series, Miami University, Oxford, Ohio, 1981 Sept. 18 (Box 39)
  - Into the Mainstream: Women's Education in the 1980's, University of Missouri, Kansas City, 1981 Oct. 1 (Box 39)
  - The Perils of Policymaking, Denison University, 1981 Oct. 8 (Box 39)
  - The Perils of Policymaking American Logistics Association, Dallas, Tex., 1981 Oct. 13 (Box 39)
  - Birmingham Southern College, Birmingham, Ala., 1981 Oct 13-14 (Box 39)
  - Women and Policymaking: New Roles for a New Era, Philadelphia Women's Network, annual dinner speaker, 1981 Oct. 15 (Box 39)
  - The Perils of Policymaking, Carol Woods Residents Association, 1981 Nov. 5 (Box 39)
  - Aging Populations in Developed and Developing Countries: Economic Policy Implications, United Nations, Vienna, Austria, 1981 Nov. 9-13 (Box 39)
  - World Economic Trends, U.S. Chamber of Commerce, Council on Trends and Perspectives, 1981 Nov. 12 (Box 39)
  - Women's Work: For Love or Money? William and Mary, 1981 Nov. 14 (Box 39)
  - Durham County Council for Women, 1981 Dec. 12 (Box 39)
  - Durham Council of Women, Durham County U.S. savings bond drive kick-off luncheon, 1982 Jan. 18 (Box 39)
  - Manhattan Group of the National Association of Bank Women, 1982 Feb. 16 (Box 39)
  - Schrank, Bob, 1982 Feb. 19 (Box 39)
  - Women in a Changing Economy, Univ. of Pennsylvania and West Chester State, 1982 Mar. 1-2 (Box 39)
  - Economic Policy: Why Doesn't it Work? Washington State, Pullman, Wash., 1982 Mar. 8-9 (Box 39)
  - Armco Management group, Marco Island, Fla., 1982 Mar. 12 (Box 39)
  - Catalyst Award dinner, N.Y., 1982 Mar. 16 (Box 39)
  - Award dinner, N.C. Citizen's Association, Raleigh, N.C., 1982 Mar. 17 (Box 40)
  - Women can Do Anything, Hollins College, 1982 Apr. 3 (Box 40)
  - Women in a Changing Economy, Cornell Univ., Ithaca, N.Y., 1982 Apr. 7 (Box 40)
  - Reflections on the State of Kentucky and the State of the Economy, The Kentuckians of N.Y., 1982 May 3 (Box 40)
  - The Brains that will Keep us Alive, Ohio Northern University, Ada, Ohio, 1982 May 4 (Box 40)
  - Rules for Success, Rules for Failure, Western Maryland College commencement, 1982 May 22, 2 folders (Box 40)
  - Rules for Success, Rules for Failure, University of Wisconsin, Green Bay, 1982 May 29 (Box 40)
  - New Challenges to the American Economy, Brandeis Univ., Waltham, Mass., cancelled, 1982 June 7 (Box 40)
  - Who Should Do What? Duke Symposium on the Social Responsiveness of Business, 1982 June 9 (Box 40)
  - 40 Years in the Wilderness, Berea, Distinguished Alumni Award, 40th reunion, 1982 July 3 (Box 40)
  - Heath Care in an Uncertain Economy, St. Francis Community Hospital, Greenville, S.C., 1982 July 18 (Box 40)
  - International Trade: Challenges for the 80's, The United States Economy, 1982, Revitalization of U.S. Industry: Problems and Policies, and Regulation, Dregulation, and the Special Case of U.S. Airlines, Australia, 1982 Aug. 20-Sept. 3, 2 folders (Box 40)
  - The Effect of Changing Economic and Business Trends on Education, Mid-Atlantic Placement Association, Lancaster, Pa., 1982 Sept. 19 (Box 41)
  - Is There Life After Creighton?: Comment on Careers, Creighton Univ., Omaha, Nebraska, 1982 Oct. 11-12 (Box 41)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund, Highest Award, Waldorf-Astoria, 1982 Oct. 27 (Box 41)
  - James Madison Univ., Harrisonburg, Va., Cancelled, 1982 Nov. 10 (Box 41)
  - Liberal Arts in the Marketplace, St. Olaf's College, Northfield, Minnesota, 1983 Feb. 14 (Box 41)
  - Appalachian Regional Commission - Workshop, Jackson, Mississippi, 1983 Apr. 11-12 (Box 41)
  - American Management Association, Introduce Walter Fallon, Dallas, Tex., 1983 Apr. 14 (Box 41)
  - The Rewards for Service and Achievement, University of S.C., 1983 Apr. 15 (Box 41)
  - Today's Professional Woman: Great Potential, A Few Problems, Dayton Women's Network, 1983 Apr. 29 (Box 41)
  - Univ. of Mass., Inauguration of Joe Duffey as Chancellor, 1983 Apr. 30 (Box 41)
  - Duke commencement, Distinguished Alumni Award, 1983 May 8 (Box 41)
  - N.C. School of Science and Mathematics, 1983 May 24 (Box 41)
  - White House Perspectives: Past and Present, Alumni Weekend Panel, 1983 June 11 (Box 41)
  - World Trade: A Call for New Leadership, American Society of Corporate Secretaries, The Greenbrier, White Sulphur Springs, West Va., 1983 June 27 (Box 41)
  - S.E.F. (South Education Fund) Atlanta Conference, 1983 Oct. 13-14 (Box 41)
  - The Changing U.S. Position in World Trade, Columbia University Distinguished Leaders Lecture Series, Graduate School of Business, 1983 Oct. 18 (Box 42)
  - Women and the Economy: A Reassessment, Governor's Conference on Women and the Economy, Raleigh, N.C., 1983 Oct. 31 (Box 42)
  - Notes on Public Policy: Can the Process Work? Houston - RJR, Aminoil Leadership Dialogue, 1983 Nov. 22-23 (Box 42)
  - Economists and Economic Policy Making, N.C. Council on Economic Education, Greensboro, 1983 Dec. 12 (Box 42)
  - The State of the Economy and Liberal Arts in the Marketplace, Agnes Scott College, 1984 Jan. 9-30 (Box 42)
  - Inside the Corporate Boardroom, Women's Network Seattle, 1984 Feb. 8 (Box 42)
  - National Network of Graduate Business School Women, Annual Conference, Chapel Hill, N.C., Cancelled Event, 1984 Feb. 25 (Box 42)
  - Comments on Corporate Decision-Making, Berkeley, Calif. Symposium, 1984 Mar. 12 (Box 42)
  - YWCA Women of Achievement (Amanda Smith), 1984 Mar. 14 (Box 42)
  - Toronto, 1984 Mar. 26 (Box 42)
  - Milwaukee Sales and Marketing Executives, 1984 Apr. 19 (Box 42)
  - Univ. of Rochester, 1984 May 6, 2 folders (Box 42)
  - On Work and Success, Grove City commencement, 1984 May 19, 2 folders (Box 42)
  - US-USSR Trade and Economic Council, 1984 May 23 (Box 43)
  - From Access to Ascent: The New Problem for Professional Women, Women in International Business Conference, 1984 May 24 (Box 43)
  - Money is Power, Orange County Women's Center, 1984 June 2 (Box 43)
  - IBM Executives, Fuqua School of Business, 1984 June 27 (Box 43)
  - Economic Issues in the Campaign, Chrysler Institute of Academic Affairs, 1984 Sept. 6 (Box 43)
  - Lenoir Rhyne Convocation, Hickory, N.C., 1984 Sept. 9-10 (Box 43)
  - Uneasy Times for Nonprofit Organizations, Rainier Bank, Seattle, 1984 Oct. 11 (Box 43)
  - Directions for the Post-Election Economy: What About the Deficits? Washington University Akin Fellowship Program, St. Louis, Missouri, 1984 Oct. 30-31, 2 folders (Box 43)
  - Charles Waldo Haskins Award, St. Regis Sheraton, N.Y., 1984 Nov. 12 (Box 43)
  - Fayetteville Women's Networth, 1984 Nov. 16 (Box 43)
  - Texas Foundation of Women's Research, Austin Tex., 1984 Nov. 30 (Box 43)
  - State of the Economy, 1985, Concordia College, Moorhead, Minn., 1985 Jan. 9-10 (Box 43)
  - The Economy in 1985: Domestic and International, East Carolina University, 1985 Feb 12-14 (Box 44)
  - On Keeping Faith with Emily Prudden, Pfeiffer College, 1985 Mar. 1 (Box 44)
  - The Economy in 1985, Peace College, Raleigh, N.C., 1985 Mar. 13 (Box 44)
  - World Trade: New Problems for the Nation and the Midwest, Adrian College, Adrian, Michigan, 1985 Mar. 28 (Box 44)
  - A Changing View of Aging, Junior League of Roanoke, Conference of Aging, 1985 Apr. 1 (Box 44)
  - Washington Capital Campaign Kick-off - Co-host with Liddy Dale, 1985 Apr. 20 (Box 44)
  - What Makes A Corporate Director Effective? Utility Women's Conference, Charlottesville, Va., 1985 May 1 (Box 44)
  - International Conference of Gerontology, Panelist, 1985 July 16 (Box 44)
  - On Leadership, American Youth Foundation, Camp Miniwanca, Shelly, Mich., 1985 Aug. 9 (Box 44)
  - Atlanta Duke Alumni, 1985 Oct. 3 (Box 44)
  - Gerontology and Geriatrics at Duke, 30th Anniversary, 1985 Oct. 10-12 (Box 44)
  - U.S. Problems in a Global Economy, Management Institute for Senior Executives - Governor's Office of Employee Relations, Albany, N.Y., 1985 Oct. 22 (Box 44)
  - U.S. Problems in a Global Economy, Sheboygan Economic Club, Sheboygan, Wisconsin, 1985 Oct. 31 (Box 44)
  - Washington Westin Cocktail Party and Dinner, 1986 Mar. 6 (Box 45)
  - Berea N.Y. Alumni Luncheon, 1986 Mar. 18 (Box 45)
  - Maintaining U.S. Competitiveness: The Role for Higher Education, American Association of State Colleges and Universities, 1986 Apr. 21 (Box 45)
  - The Future Isn't What It Used To Be, Berea College Women's History Month, 1986 Apr. 22 (Box 45)
  - Duke commencement, 1986 May 4, 2 folders (Box 45)
  - Funds for the Needy: Who Is Responsible? Presbyterian Church Foundation, Minneapolis, Minn., 1986 June 13 (Box 45)
  - Traditional Industries in the South: The Challenge, Southern Governors' annual meeting, Charlotte, N.C., 1986 Aug. 11 (Box 45)
  - Bald Head Conference (Charlie Rose), 1986 Sept. 6 (Box 45)
  - Sex in the Marketplace Revisited, Notre Dame College of Ohio, 1986 Sept. 22 (Box 45)
  - Class of 1946 Reunion, 1986 Nov. 7 (Box 45)
  - Policy Making in a Global Economy, Davidson College, 1987 Jan. 14 (Box 45)
  - John De Butts, 1987 Jan. 25 (Box 45)
  - The Economy in 1978-88: Surprises? Disappointments? Charlotte Business Men, 1987 Feb. 3 (Box 45)
  - Policy Making in a Global Economy, Washington and Lee, 1987 Feb. 9-11 (Box 45)
  - Conference on Responsibilities of Directors, 1987 Mar. 20 (Box 45)
  - Policy Making in a Global Economy, Northern Illinois University, Dekalb, Illinois, 1987 Mar. 24 (Box 46)
  - Duke Haiti Conference, 1987 Mar. 30 (Box 46)
  - Charlotte Duke Alumni, 1987 Apr. 7 (Box 46)
  - A Corporate View: What Do Directors Expect of the CEO? National Forum on Hospital and Health Affairs, Duke Univ., 1987 May 1 (Box 46)
  - On Work and Success, commencement address, Penn State-Behrend College, Erie, Pa., 1987 May 17 (Box 46)
  - Industrial Achievement Award, National Association of Bank Women, 1987 June 10 (Box 46)
  - The Economy: Problems and Policies of the 1980s, Women's History The Future Isn't What it Used to Be, and Education for Careers in the Global Marketplace, De Pauw Univ., 1987 Oct. 6-8 (Box 46)
  - National Association of Corporate Directors, 1987 Oct. 19 (Box 46)
  - Oustanding Alumni of Kentucky Award, 1987 Oct. 27-28 (Box 46)